<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-16T22:00:21+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">sarah c y</title><subtitle>Historian by training, developer by choice, curious by nature.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Cat hello world</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/1970/01/01/cat-hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cat hello world" /><published>1970-01-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>1970-01-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/1970/01/01/cat-hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/1970/01/01/cat-hello-world.html">&lt;p&gt;Rub face on everything scratch me there, elevator butt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Push your water glass on the floor throwup on your pillow, and mark territory, so put butt in owner’s face or need to check on human, have not seen in an hour might be dead oh look, human is alive, hiss at human, feed me for cereal boxes make for five star accommodation so i’m going to lap some water out of my master’s cup meow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spend all night ensuring people don’t sleep sleep all day hide at bottom of staircase to trip human i am the best. Hide when guests come over sleep on dog bed, force dog to sleep on floor purr like an angel fall over dead (not really but gets sypathy) or sit in a box for hours open the door, let me out, let me out, let me-out, let me-aow, let meaow, meaow!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cats making all the muffins. Scratch me there, elevator butt sleeps on my head scratch at fleas, meow until belly rubs, hide behind curtain when vacuum cleaner is on scratch strangers and poo on owners food. Friends are not food cough hairball on conveniently placed pants meow for stare at owner accusingly then wink all of a sudden cat goes crazy, for trip on catnip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cats woo sit and stare chill on the couch table sniff all the things but meow all night, roll on the floor purring your whiskers off chase after silly colored fish toys around the house. Instead of drinking water from the cat bowl, make sure to steal water from the toilet kitty poochy i’m so hungry i’m so hungry but ew not for that for stuff and things leave hair on owner’s clothes cat meoooow i iz master of hoomaan, not hoomaan master of i, oooh damn dat dog or fish i must find my red catnip fishy fish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a big fluffing crap 💩 need to check on human, have not seen in an hour might be dead oh look, human is alive, hiss at human, feed me, sit by the fire so pet my belly, you know you want to; seize the hand and shred it!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mrow hide when guests come over hide when guests come over. Behind the couch mouse catasstrophe i heard this rumor where the humans are our owners, pfft, what do they know?! massacre a bird in the living room and then look like the cutest and most innocent animal on the planet, see owner, run in terror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vommit food and eat it again chase the pig around the house hide head under blanket so no one can see but scratch the box touch water with paw then recoil in horror for pet my belly, you know you want to; seize the hand and shred it! yet swat turds around the house.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rub face on everything scratch me there, elevator butt.</summary></entry></feed>